[
	{"question": "ア", "answer": "a"},
	{"question": "イ", "answer": "i"},
	{"question": "ウ", "answer": "u"},
	{"question": "エ", "answer": "e"},
	{"question": "オ", "answer": "o"},
	{"question": "カ", "answer": "ka"},
	{"question": "キ", "answer": "ki"},
	{"question": "ク", "answer": "ku"},
	{"question": "ケ", "answer": "ke"},
	{"question": "コ", "answer": "ko"},
	{"question": "サ", "answer": "sa"},
	{"question": "シ", "answer": "shi"},
	{"question": "ス", "answer": "su"},
	{"question": "セ", "answer": "se"},
	{"question": "ソ", "answer": "so"},
	{"question": "タ", "answer": "ta"},
	{"question": "千", "answer": "chi"},
	{"question": "ツ", "answer": "tsu"},
	{"question": "テ", "answer": "te"},
	{"question": "ト", "answer": "to"},
	{"question": "ナ", "answer": "na"},
	{"question": "二", "answer": "ni"},
	{"question": "ヌ", "answer": "nu"},
	{"question": "ネ", "answer": "ne"},
	{"question": "ノ", "answer": "no"},
	{"question": "刃", "answer": "ha"},
	{"question": "ヒ", "answer": "hi"},
	{"question": "フ", "answer": "hu"},
	{"question": "へ", "answer": "he"},
	{"question": "ホ", "answer": "ho"},
	{"question": "マ", "answer": "ma"},
	{"question": "ミ", "answer": "mi"},
	{"question": "ム", "answer": "mu"},
	{"question": "メ", "answer": "me"},
	{"question": "モ", "answer": "mo"},
	{"question": "ヤ", "answer": "ya"},
	{"question": "ユ", "answer": "yu"},
	{"question": "ヨ", "answer": "yo"},
	{"question": "ラ", "answer": "ra"},
	{"question": "リ", "answer": "ri"},
	{"question": "ル", "answer": "ru"},
	{"question": "レ", "answer": "re"},
	{"question": "ロ", "answer": "ro"},
	{"question": "ワ", "answer": "wa"},
	{"question": "ヲ", "answer": "wo"},
	{"question": "ン", "answer": "n"},
]